(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
-Surprise!
Hello, son?
We're here at your brother's place.
Do you want to drop by?
Babe…
Why are you being so noisy?
If I leave,
how will you build a case
against the Moravianos?
I'm sure I'll find a way.
Hey!
-I'll cook.
-No, no.
I think we need to follow a new lead.
Are you sure you won't betray us?
I have a family.
I also have a family to protect!
Please have mercy.
My dear…
I'll take care of it.
I don't want complications in our plans.
Sir…
Unfortunately,
she grew up in my world.
Papa!
Chiara? She looks so naive!
But you know Chiara,
when I checked her profile,
she looks so harmless.
You know, I wouldn't wonder
and be surprised
if she's nothing
but a second-rate, trying hard,
spoiled brat!
And just in case
Chiara knows what her parents are doing,
specifically her father,
Why do you keep targeting Chiara?
To be honest,
is it because Mikoy
still hasn't called you?
And he's still not sure
if he wants to continue
the mission with us?
And this guy Mikoy?
I don't see even the slightest bit
of proactiveness in him.
You know people like Mikoy,
I feel like they'd rather choose
the easy way out than to fight.
Because he's weak.
And that's where you're wrong.
Really?
But why hasn't he called you until now?
He still hasn't made a decision.
Bok… You know, you're
even worse than those
boyfriends or girlfriends
or partners who ghost people!
Anyway, maybe my delivery arrived.
I'll be back.
That's yours now.
That's my extra toothbrush, anyway.
Instead of you borrowing mine.
That girl is crazy!
She didn't even say thank you?
I feel like I’ve been treated badly.
And that's it?
And who was she, anyway?
-I’ll ask Ma’am if she’s busy.
-Okay.
Thank you.
Ms. Tess!
-Oh…
-Hello.
You know me?
Actually, I don’t.
But because of those
boxes of cake you're carrying,
I was able to guess.
Are you Mikoy's friend?
Uh, kind of…
It’s something like that.
But Alex is actually the one he knows.
But anyway, he mentioned
that your Cebu cake is really delicious!
So we ended up ordering.
Well then, here is your order delivery.
Good thing we visited Mikoy.
Rather than sending it by courier,
we just delivered it ourselves, right?
-Yes.
-I'm sure Alex will be happy about that.
What's your name, son?
Sianong, sir!
And what is your name?
I’m Mikoy's father, Mario.
Oh, right.
Oh, just a second.
Here's the payment,
-Oh!
-Ms. Tess.
Thank you very much!
Oh my!
This is too much.
It's okay!
This was even a special delivery from you.
So the extra there is your tip.
-Thank you very much!
-You even went through the trouble.
Sianong… What kind of agency is this?
We're the agency that handles
transnational crimes,
especially for us Filipinos
who face crimes while abroad.
So you're an investigator? Police?
-Just kidding, sir!
-You're too much!
-I was just kidding! You…
-You're too much.
Just to make our morning fun!
-Just kidding. It’s something like that.
-I see.
We're police officers.
Will we be able to meet Alex?
She has a meeting.
But please don't worry, Ms. Tess.
I'll personally tell her
that you were the ones
who brought this here.
Thank you very much, okay?
You're welcome.
Oh, I'll head out first, okay?
-Sure.
-Goodbye, Ms. Tess.
Mr. Mario and…
I’m Betchay.
Betchay, okay!
-Betchay.
-Hello. Good morning.
-All right!
-There’s the cake.
-Okay.
-All right.
-Thank you!
-Please take the cakes.
-Thank you, miss.
-Okay, thank you.
-Okay!
-Take care!
-We got a tip!
See, I told you.
We have extra profit!
No way. That's too expensive!
Just get some ice cream.
-Ice cream.
-Come on!
There, sir. These are
our favorite drivers.
-There…
-Sir, good afternoon.
Hello, sir.
Oh…
This little thing, it's nothing to them.
Mikoy Pinagpala…
I finally found you!
No problem, boss.
If there's a problem,
don't hesitate to call me.
-Yes, sir.
-Okay.
Manager, Santos is late again.
I don't know where he keeps going.
He said there was traffic
on the road again.
Oh! Boss, sorry!
I didn't realize you were there.
No. It's fine.
So, what's the problem here?
Why is Santos always late?
Oh, it's nothing, Boss!
We have a container van that sometimes
arrives late at the port.
So most of the time,
the drivers sleep at the stopover.
Or sometimes,
for whatever reason,
the trip gets delayed.
We have a theory in the office
about how the cargo is being moved.
While the container vans
are on their way to the port,
some of them take a different route
to switch the cargo.
That’s normal, sir.
Give me a report about it.
I just want to know
if we can help our drivers.
Oh, Boss!
Don't worry about it.
I'll take care of it!
Those drivers are just stubborn.
I'll be the one to discipline them.
Hey! Get inside!
-Hey! Hey!
-Get inside!
-Oh!
-Don't be noisy!
-Okay.
-Get in!
-Okay, wait.
-Hurry up!
Get in!
Look, guys!
Sweet cake from Cebu.
PINAGPALA
SPECIAL BAKESHOP
This was freshly baked
just three days ago.
Okay?
You could say it's like an antique,
but it has a modern taste.
-Looks delicious.
-And according to
the Association of All Gym Goers,
this is public enemy number one.
Because it ruins your diet.
It’s so delicious, you can't resist it,
even if you’re a gym goer.
You know that feeling?
It’s addictive! So, look! Try it!
-Come on! Dara! Come on! Try! Dara!
-Look, he's enjoying it.
Go ahead! Come on!
So delicious! Delicious! So good!
Feels like heaven!
What happened to your faces?
I get it.
It’s really delicious, right?
It’s so delicious,
you just end up speechless.
Right, Dara?
Or maybe you’re acting that way
because the boss is behind me.
And he's jealous of us!
You want some cake, sir?
Sianong…
In my office.
Alex!
Let’s clean up.
-Go ahead.
-Here.
Hurry up!
Wait! Easy, bro!
Who are you?
Wait, what do you need?
Wait, is this a hold-up?
Bro, I’m not rich, okay?
And I just started working here.
And this car, this is not mine!
This is just a company car. Promise!
What is this?
Some amateur acting school?
Pretending like you
don’t know anything? Hey!
Don’t act smart!
If it weren’t for you,
my brother would still be alive!
Huh? Hold on!
What are you talking about?
And how am I involved
in your brother's death?
Also, an important question,
who is your brother?
Just a moment.
Can you press on the photos?
Press it.
There. Right there.
-Him!
-Huh?
He’s handsome.
Wait.
We’re twins. He’s my brother.
That explains it.
Literally, the spitting image
of each other.
But if you ask me,
you look better than him.
-Just a little, okay?
-Are you joking?
If you’re joking, it’s not funny!
Huh!
I’m sorry! Come on.
I just want you to relax.
Because you might
do something you’ll regret.
I’ll regret?!
If anyone should regret anything,
it’s that Czech Viktor guy!
That bald one!
I’m his nightmare!
In English…
I’m going to kill you first.
To send a message to Viktor
that he will be the next one
I’ll take down for my brother!
NORBERTO S. RUIZ
Tell me, Agent Alex and Agent Sianong.
Did I imagine seeing
Mikoy’s parents here in our office?
The parents of our very own asset?
Actually, sir, it was my idea.
And your idea was to order
and have the cake delivered?
Because we received
a credible threat to his life.
But for reasons unknown to us,
he did not answer our calls.
And because of that,
I called their bakery’s direct hotline
and pretended to be a customer.
I didn’t expect that his mom and dad
would personally deliver it to our office.
You two are becoming very careless.
Don’t do anything
that could ruin your mission, okay?
Do you have a full profile of the parents?
Uh, yes, sir.
And as far as I know,
there are no red flags.
They are just simple people.
Are you sure?
Yes, sir.
Why, sir?
Do we have a problem?
Do you know these people?
Okay. Okay.
But before anything else,
before you kill me, let's break that down.
First,
before calling him bald,
we know he has lost his hair.
We don’t need to call him bald, right?
We don’t even know
what he’s going through.
That’s why his hair doesn’t grow back.
-Is that so?
-Come on. Yes!
Sorry about that.
There you go!
Seriously!
Second,
if you really want to get back at him,
why do you need to kill me
to send him a message? Right?
Just go straight to him.
Go straight to the point!
No more beating around the bush!
And third, if you really
want to get back at him,
don’t kill me.
Because honestly, I can actually help you.
Believe it or not,
What do you mean by that?
Send me again
the full profile of his family.
And make sure
you stay away from his family.
We don’t want any more innocent people
getting caught up in this mess.
Copy, sir.
Okay, sir.
We should not proceed with the demolition!
There are innocent people within the area.
Our mission is our mission.
And we must achieve our objectives,
no matter what it takes!
You know, that girl is such a weirdo!
Anyway, I just woke up,
and she was already next to me in bed.
It was like we were really roommates.
Maybe she really is your roommate?
No! Can I really have a roommate
without me knowing?
And we’re all boys!
You know what? Lock your door properly.
So no one can just walk right in.
I locked it!
I have no idea how she still managed
to get into my room.
So, what do you want?
Should we call the police?
The police, really?
There’s no need. It’s too much hassle.
I don't want to go back
to the police station.
You know that I'm already traumatized.
If you want, let's just adopt a dog.
-Right?
-Oh!
-It seems fun here.
-It's allowed.
Bros, look who’s here.
What do you mean?
How can you help me against Viktor?
Because I'm not just one
of Viktor's normal employees. Okay?
What do you mean you're not normal?
Are you a paranormal?
Are you messing with me?!
No! Come on!
It's just hard to explain.
I can't exactly tell you.
But anyway, I'm not your enemy, okay?
Actually, I'm on your side.
So, what are you saying?
You're some kind of police agent
who infiltrated Viktor's company?
And you're the key to exposing
all of his criminal activities?
The one who's going
to bring him down? Is that it?
Yes.
Something like that.
You're good.
I already have so many problems!
And now you're adding to them!
You know, you're such a funny guy!
It’s really a shame to kill you.
Because the world would lose its joy.
You know, if I were you,
I’d stop watching too much
Jason Bourne!
James Bond!
All sorts of things
are getting into your head!
I’m not lying, I promise!
It’s true!
I’m secretly working for the police.
So if you’ll kill me, that’s it!
Our whole operation will be ruined.
We’ll never be able to bring Viktor down.
Do you want that, huh?
Bro, what happened to you?
Ever since you got out of jail,
you haven’t been hanging out with us.
It makes me feel like
you don’t want to be friends
with me anymore.
Angelito.
I’m having trouble with drafting.
And I know you can help me.
Right?
Owen, I’m sorry, okay?
I also have a lot of school requirements.
I still have so much to finish.
So, you’re rejecting me?
You’re turning down my request?
It’s not like that, Owen.
But you know,
you can’t always depend on others
for our course requirements.
Honestly,
you need to learn how
to figure things out yourself.
That’s why we’re here in school, right?
To learn.
All right. How about this?
If you help me,
we’ll be the best of friends.
But if you won't help me,
you might regret it.
I expect my plates tomorrow, okay?
Boys, let's go.
-Let's go.
-Come on!
Hey! Okay!
If you pull that out,
I'm going to shoot up your head!
-Just relax!
-Do it slowly.
Oh!
You don't want to believe me.
I just want to prove to you
that I'm telling the truth.
Here it is. I’ll call
my police handler. Okay?
Director Norberto is right.
We shouldn’t involve Mikoy’s family.
It doesn't matter, Bok.
You know, as long
as Mikoy isn’t calling you,
it doesn't really matter.
But I can’t blame him either.
This is really a tough job.
And the only ones who can spy
on syndicates like the Moravianos
are the people who are strong and brave.
-It’s Mikoy.
-Oh, go for it! What are you waiting for?
Answer the call.
-Hello?
Special Agent Alex?
This is Mikoy.
Honestly, I didn’t expect you to call.
But I’m very happy
to hear your voice again.
Looks like we have a lot to talk about.
Exactly!
That’s why I really want to meet you.
And bring a burger, okay?
And extra fries!
Sure! Where are you?
Just here at the Annex parking.
And hurry up!
I’m starving!
All right, no problem.
Okay. Thank you!
So, what happened? What’s the problem?
Mikoy is in trouble.
He just gave us a distress signal!
Burger with extra fries!
-Let’s go!
-We move in two minutes!
We’re coming in hot!
You know, that is impressive.
After everything, he still remembered
his distress signal.
So, stop underestimating him.
Mikoy knows what he’s doing.
He knows what kind of trouble
he’s getting into.
So, let’s move quickly.
We cannot afford anything
to happen to our asset.
Okay! Let’s go!
So, there you go.
Do you believe it now?
Agent Alex will explain it to you.
What do you think of me?
Stupid?
You’re tricking me!
I know what you did.
That’s a code!
Bring burger with extra fries?
What do you think of me?
Someone who doesn’t watch Netflix?
I know you called your men for backup!
No!
I just really love burgers!
Promise!
If you really love burgers,
which tastes better,
Burger McJo or Burger Queen?
Huh? Huh?!
Answer!
McJo?
Wrong! There’s no right answer,
because both are delicious!
Ahh! Hey!
Hey, funny boy!
Help!
Funny boy!
The subscriber cannot be reached…
Mikoy, where are you?
Why can’t I contact you?
The subscriber cannot be reached…
Mikoy!
Mikoy! Where are you?
You and I know we need to protect him.
And I don’t want him to get involved
in our plans here in the Philippines.
He must never go into
the syndicates that do evil things.
But will he accept who you really are?
I want to fully commit on this mission.
I’m ready to help you
take down the Moravianos.