(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
Because he is now
the new Chief Operations Officer
of Vertex Global Holdings.
The company of the Valtrovis.
Bro? Bro, is that really you?
My brother!
You look like a big shot now.
Hello, Angelito.
Chiara Valtrovi.
Mikoy is in danger.
Someone wants to kill him.
Because now you're the one
in a complicated situation.
Hopefully next time, you'll knock, huh.
There's a reason why I needed
to come to your apartment secretly.
So no one sees us meeting.
Isn't there a lot
of CCTV in this building?
And we discovered
that there are many dead spots
in the CCTV coverage.
Like at the fire exit
and service elevators.
What are you doing here?
You already know why I came here.
Do you have any
new information to give us?
Easy, I just started.
I'm still studying
the company's operations.
Look, I need more time to understand
how Vertex is used
for the movement of illegal cargo.
I don't even know
what illegal cargo they're exporting.
Also, can you leave now?
Chiara might show up again later.
We might get caught again.
Don't worry.
Sianong is monitoring them,
and according to his information,
they flew with Viktor to Hong Kong.
Do you have any idea
what they'll do in Hong Kong?
They went to Disneyland?
I don't know. Went shopping, maybe?
I was too busy earlier at the office.
I'm sorry if I'm pressuring you.
I just want to make sure
we didn't miss any details.
I know I already agreed with you.
I will stand by that.
Me too.
I also want to finish this
as soon as possible.
But for me,
I haven't noticed anything
suspicious at the office.
For now, it seems…
all their operations look legit.
We have a theory at the office
on how they move the cargo.
Where the exports are packaged.
But our theory is
while the container vans
are on the way to the port,
some of them take a re-route
to change the packages.
They go to a secret location.
And in that secret location,
they ship the illegal cargo.
Is that AI?
Well, the syndicate looks stupid.
It's Sianong's idea.
He's kind of obsessed now
with AI-generated videos.
And he made this
so you can better visualize
how the Moravianos operate.
Oh, really?
You know, tell Sianong he's being stupid.
What does he think of me?
I don't have imagination?
You know, between the two of us,
he seems more clueless.
You know, I have a theory about him.
No one will really love him.
He'll grow old alone.
Do you know why?
Because I really don't see
any good character traits in him
that would make someone love him.
None at all.
Be careful.
Because he can see and hear you.
How?
You've got some nerve.
You're still sabotaging me.
Backstabber!
You put surveillance in my condo?
We need to monitor you.
Because your apartment
is the most vulnerable spot.
And very real. And…
the intelligence we got
from Agent Kian is actionable,
that someone wants to kill you.
Couldn't you at least have told me?
I've been walking around here
naked for days.
And then you set up these things?
You actually have cameras?
My God.
Can't you look at me?
You saw something?
He's good.
What are you doing?
And you even made me
a scandal in your office?
Wow!
Fine then!
Good thing I make you happy.
Don't worry, I already talked to them.
Gosh!
"I talked to them."
I'm sure, you also enjoyed seeing me
look like a fool in that video.
Is that really how shallow you think I am?
I understand the difficult situation
I put you in.
And I admire you.
Because despite my blackmail attempts,
you still trusted me.
If you're really struggling
and you don't want to continue,
you can walk away from this mission.
I won't stop you.
I'll let you leave.
Really?
Alex, what are you doing?
Do you know what you're doing right now?
Why are you giving an exit option
to our only asset?
Let me make this clear.
You're saying it's okay with you
if I don't continue spying on them?
Against the Moravianos?
Hello, Alex?
Why are you giving an exit option
for Mr. Pinagpala?
Are you out--
Alex!
Hello?
I think your partner heard you.
Between Sianong and me,
I'm the senior officer.
Is this a trap?
Maybe later,
you'll suddenly lock up my brother.
I'm just giving you the option
to not do this.
And you're right.
We started on the wrong foot.
I blackmailed you,
so you would agree to this position.
And I don't think that was the right way.
If I'm going to take down the Moravianos,
I will do it the right way.
And I won't force an innocent
and good person like you.
Think about it carefully, Mikoy.
Just continue this mission
if you want to do it,
and if it really comes from your heart.
Oh my goodness! It's Chiara!
If I leave,
how will you build a case
against the Moravianos?
I'm sure I can find a way.
But it won't be easy.
But I won't give up on the Moravianos.
And I won't stop until they're imprisoned
because that's the right thing.
Alex!
Alex, answer…
the phone!
It's Chiara.
Hey!
How are you?
You already missed me so much.
Yes, of course.
Come on.
What are you doing?
What are you doing here?
I thought you were in Hong Kong?
Papa had a business meeting, and then,
I took that chance to go shopping.
But we have to go home.
Wait, how did you know we had
a quick getaway in Hong Kong?
I think you mentioned it to me.
Or maybe your mom?
Yes, maybe it was Mom.
She can't stop talking about you.
She really wanted you to join
the shopping trip, but I said,
"Mama, no.
Because he's really busy with Vertex."
But she insisted, since
it's just a short visit, anyway.
You know, you guys are intense, huh?
Turning Hong Kong into Cubao.
Have you eaten?
Not yet.
I was going to cook, but…
-Well, let me cook something for you.
-Oh, no, no.
You know, let's just eat out.
My treat. Okay?
-No need.
-No.
-You'll just get more tired.
-Please.
-No, I promise, I won't get tired.
-Forget it.
-I'll cook.
-No, no.
I seldom cook.
Have you eaten already?
It's nothing. It's just a mess.
I told you so.
Mikoy?
Are you okay?
Sweetheart, just relax there.
I'm almost done.
Okay?
Sweetheart, do you know
where my charger is?
-Maybe in the room?
-Oh, no.
Just keep cooking, okay?
-What happened?
-I don't know.
Maybe there's a fire.
Come on. Let's just go down.
-Come on. Let's go.
-Look--
What are you doing?
Why are you compromising our mission?
Look at what you've been doing.
You almost put yourself in danger.
I'm just doing what I think is right.
What you think is right?
Then why did you let our own asset leave?
I had to do that.
For Mikoy to be an effective asset,
he has to believe in our mission,
and he has to do it willingly.
May I remind you
how we set up Mikoy and his brother
so that he would I agree to this mission?
You think people will just willingly
do the right thing?
Without threatening them?
Without giving them a warning?
Agent Alex, that's fake news!
Because the truth is,
most people will choose the easier option
rather than what's right.
Hello, Metro Manila.
Dad? Mom?
Our son is handsome!
Wow!
Give me a hug, son!
You're so handsome.
Wait, what is this for?
Is it my birthday?
Well…
I was really bothered
by how you looked last night.
You looked really stressed.
So I called Mom and Dad for you.
Actually, it worked out
because we had a big order here in Manila.
And when we were told
we'd ride on a private jet,
of course, who are we, so naturally,
well, a private jet,
and we'll save money too.
-Right?
-What?
We have an order in Manila?
Nice!
Looks like our social media marketing
is working there, huh?
Oh dear!
The one who ordered is your friend.
-My friend?
-That's right.
Yes.
The name was Alex.
They even asked me.
They said, "Where is he?"
I said, "He's here in Manila."
You're already here
because you got a new job
at Chiara's company.
Who's that friend of yours, sweetheart?
Actually, I can't really say
if it's a friend.
You know, it's like
we just know each other.
How did you guys meet?
How did I even meet?
Actually, I don't even know.
It's been a long time. I don't know.
Dear, why don't you message,
or why don't you message on Fishbook?
That's right, too,
because it's important to have
someone you know here in Manila.
So that sometimes
you have company for drinks.
That's right.
You know what?
We were worried about Chiara's message.
Are you stressed out with your new job?
Mom, I'm okay.
Of course, it's natural
to still adjust a little.
It's a new job after all.
Even during my first months
as a waiter in Prague,
I was totally exhausted too.
But I'll get used to it.
I can handle it, right?
That's why I thought maybe it would help
if Mom and Dad were here for now.
So you can reduce some of your stress.
What about Angelito?
He doesn't have classes today, right?
What? You're so noisy!
If you don't want to sleep,
let others sleep!
What the!
Who's this girl?
Hello, son!
We're here with your brother.
Do you want to drop by?
You don't have class today, right?
Mom.
I really need to finish something.
Why are you whispering?
You're also whispering.
No…
Okay. Son!
We're just here.
We brought your favorite
ube-flavored cake.
Okay.
I'll come right away.
Wait, what are you busy with?
Hopefully it's not just studying,
or your brain will turn into cake.
Yes, brother.
I really need to finish something.
But I'll come there right away, okay?
Why are you so noisy?
What was that?
She said "babe"?
Nice!
Our baby Angelito is grown up!
He said "babe".
-You think that's funny?
-No class--
There's no class!
Doing PE in the room!
And also…
Bro,
you need to come here.
I need your help.
I don't even know how
she got into my room.
Bro, do I look like someone
for an organic encounter?
No, as far as I know, I was just sleeping,
and when I woke up,
she was already beside me in bed.
Seriously, I don't know!
Hey!
Do you have a toothbrush?
And also, can I borrow this?
Oh.
Okay, sir.
Is what I read in Sianong's report true?
You offered our asset,
Mikoy, an option out?
Yes, sir.
And I'm sorry, sir,
if the decision seems
illogical or impulsive.
But when I talked to Mikoy,
I felt his struggle.
But just know,
without Mikoy,
your work will become harder.
You can count on me.
What now?
You got scolded badly by the boss, right?
He was really disappointed
with the decisions you made.
Imagine,
that's our agency director,
and he was really mad at you.
Totally, Bok.
Not only scolded, he almost exploded.
I almost turned into a sponge.
Mikoy is an important asset,
you know that.
So we can't just let him leave.
Bok.
The important thing now is to find out
when he will answer us.
Whether he is willing
to fight for us or not.
I don't want to wait and just rely
on Mikoy's decision.
So?
What's your plan?
What do you mean?
I think we need to focus our energy
on Chiara Valtrovi.
Because it's already
known in the whole town,
it's about to explode!
The name…
Angelo!
I have a strong feeling
that she knows something about all this.
And she is the key
to bringing down the Moravianos.
Of course!
-The one and only.
-There, right there.
Of course!
You're something else!
Chiara, thank you so much.
You know, next time,
you don't need to do this.
You went through all this trouble.
It wasn't any trouble because,
to be honest, I wasn't really doing much.
You know, it's actually okay.
Mom told me earlier that they
would stay with me first.
You?
Are you just staying here?
I mean,
aren't you going to Prague anymore?
Well, I already talked to Dad about it,
and I might stay here for now.
Maybe Mom and the others
will go back to Prague.
Of course!
Could I say no?
Of course, I want you to be here always.
So, if possible, don't leave anymore.
Please?
All right, you still have a lot to do.
Bye!
Okay.
Bye.
I heard that you want to kill Mikoy.
Are you sure?
Are you sure you will never betray us?
Have mercy.
I have a family.
I also have a family
that I need to protect.
The Valtrovi family.
Have mercy.
I want to commit to this mission fully.
I'm ready to help you
bring down the Moravianos.
We both know what we need to protect him.
Because Mikoy is a good man.
And I don't want him to get involved
with what we're doing here
in the Philippines.
Pinagpala, this is your end!
-Agent Alex!
-Are you okay?
Wait, stop tickling me!
Gosh.
I hope you can make time for us.
I promise, I'll make it up to you.
How does Mr. Pinagpala make it up?
MANILA ZOOLOGICAL &amp; BOTANICAL GARDEN
I know that you like him so much.
But will he accept who you are?