(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
[rock music playing]
I want to understand irrational numbers.
[Eui-ju] Understand? Me?
Why?
Why what?
CHAPTER 29: SOMETIMES,
THE TRUTH CAN BE DANGEROUS
Uh… Why…
Why is it that
Pythagoras killed his student in the end?
Don't you get it?
Pythagoras couldn't stand the thought that
his world could collapse in a second.
5TH CENTURY BC
[playful music plays]
[exhales sharply]
-[gasps]
-What's the matter?
[stutters] Master.
PYTHAGOREAN MATH ACADEMY
CROTON, GREECE
Have you…
PYTHAGORAS, DIRECTOR
…perhaps discovered something new?
HIPPASUS, STUDENT
I tried to express
the length of the diagonal
of a unit square.
And I tried to do it as a fraction.
That's right. Every number can
be expressed as a ratio of integers.
It's the absolute truth we teach.
[Eui-ju] Well…
It's just that, it doesn't work.
-[sighs]
-What's that?
The thing is
this number cannot be expressed
as a fraction!
Wait.
Wait a minute. [breathing shakily]
All right.
Prove it to me.
-[playful music plays]
-Okay.
Okay.
Got a square.
Please watch.
-[sighs]
-[buzzer sounds]
I can't express it.
-[sobbing] I just can't.
-[gasps]
If you're right then,
it means everything we've believed
up until now is just wrong.
Have you…
told anyone else about this?
I haven't.
I haven't told anyone else about it yet.
I wanted to tell you first, master.
[sighs] I see.
That's a relief.
Hippasus.
Yes?
Your proof
-never existed in the first place.
-[dramatic music plays]
[grunting] Master.
The truth can be far too dangerous.
[echoes] Master!
[sighs]
Irrational numbers meant the collapse
of his entire world.
[Eui-ju sighs] He's such a math geek.
His eyes light up
whenever he talks about math. It's freaky.
Man.
But then again…
[sighs] …it's kind of cool.
[yelps]
Are you okay?
[stutters] Y-Yes. I'm… I'm okay. [grunts]
That's why you shouldn't space out
when you walk.
Right.
How embarrassing.
That doesn't count as embarrassing to you,
does it?
They say doing something embarrassing
boosts your creativity.
Ah.
So you're intentionally embarrassing
yourself? Is there anything more?
It's not embarrassing
if I tell you in advance.
I see. Go for the boost then.
I'm rooting for you.
EPISODE 9
I'm home.
[Ma] Oh! Go to the bathroom first.
-[people talking on television]
-Huh? I'm okay.
You can hardly do number two
when you're out.
So the moment you come home, you have
to go straight to the bathroom, okay?
And hey. [clicks tongue]
If you need to go, don't hold it.
Just please make sure you go.
[grunts] Okay!
I can take care of it myself.
You don't have to tell me
even when I have to poop.
It's because you can't take care of it
on your own! [clicks tongue]
Okay!
I'll go.
Geez.
Maybe I should pay a personal visit
to your homeroom teacher.
[stutters] Why?
He carried you all the way to the ER
on his back.
That's something to be awfully sorry
and grateful for.
Oh, no. There's no need to.
I told him I was grateful.
And he's busy.
Don't ever reach out to him or anything.
Don't do it ever, never!
You're afraid of him, aren't you?
Fair enough.
Judging by all the demerits you got,
no wonder you're scared of him.
[chuckles] Man,
that teacher must be brutal.
You really got on his bad side.
No, I mean… It's not that bad.
He's just a little…
a little blunt, I guess?
He can be kind of prickly sometimes.
But the truth is that
he's truly good at heart, you know?
He's immature and childish at times.
But he is truly good at heart.
Heart.
[playful music plays]
[dog whines]
-[owl hooting]
-[exhales]
I get it.
Smart people are known to be good
at manipulating others however they want.
That makes sense.
I have been manipulated.
I've been manipulated just like Mr. Yoon.
After nagging and scolding you ten times,
they say one nice thing,
and then you're like,
"Oh? Maybe they're actually
a good person after all."
Yeah, that's exactly how it works.
[chuckles]
Really. He's so mean to me all the time,
but I suddenly have butterflies
in my stomach
just because he said
he'd try to understand me?
It's ridiculous!
[sighs]
You better snap out of it, Yeo Eui-ju.
Don't even make eye contact
with Math from tomorrow on.
CHAPTER 30: SOMEONE
I SHOULDN'T AND CAN'T LIKE
Hey, guys.
Did you read the article I sent?
Professor Na Deul-i
has been named the First-ever
Korean Recipient of the Fields Medal.
What about it?
Do you know her?
No, I don't.
But Woo-su does.
Oh!
She was his Olympiad mate
from middle school.
Really?
[Dong-ju] Really?
Aren't you jealous?
Don't you think that
it should've been you?
[sighs] If you hadn't given up
on that Olympiad.
Actually, only if you had
gone and studied abroad…
-[Gi-jeon clears throat]
-Stop it, Da-ju.
Listen, I always knew he'd make it.
I just never thought he'd be here
eating toast with me
and arguing with those math dropouts.
-I'm talking about my friend, Ga Woo-su.
-[Gi-jeon sighs]
Ga Woo-su, my genius friend!
[sighs] Whatever.
If he'd brought glory to Korea
-by winning a Fields Medal--
-Stop.
Shut it. [clicks tongue]
So what if that professor won the medal?
Hey.
Do you even know what a Fields Medal is?
I do. And?
Then why don't you tell me who
the very first Fields Medal winner was.
-David Copperfield.
-[sighs] I'm done.
I refuse to waste my words on someone
who doesn't know that.
[Gi-jeon scoffs]
Anyway, Woo-su…
[sighs] I'm done talking to you too.
Enjoy your breakfast.
I wonder when he'll head out.
[giggles]
He usually comes out around this time.
Did I forget anything?
Did I forget all my textbooks?
I should grab my puffer. [chuckles]
Why isn't he coming out?
We're gonna be late. [chuckles]
[Gi-jeon, Da-ju speaking]
[Gi-jeon] Da-ju, hurry up!
It's been an hour since Woo-su left!
-[Da-ju] He's driving me nuts.
-What the heck?
-[Eui-ju] What time is it?
-Hurry up. We're late.
[groans] He's always like this.
Isn't that Eui-ju?
It's Eui-ju.
She's late too.
[students] Good morning.
Hello.
[Eui-ju] Why does he
flip his hair like that?
Let's get started right away.
[Eui-ju] Why does he roll up his sleeve?
Why are his fingers so long?
[gentle music playing]
[chuckles]
Why does he drink water like that?
[sighs]
He's spinning his pen.
He's so… [inhales]
He's so…
so annoying.
[grunts]
What is it that you wanna tell me?
Come and sit here first.
[sighs]
Go-ya.
You know that fangirling used to be
my only joy in life.
I know.
Of course, I am aware that
they were all from a different world,
but my love for every one of them
was always honest and real.
Thinking about those characters
gave me the strength to keep going.
But now…
every time he crosses my mind…
Oh, geez! I get so mad!
[grunts]
I really don't wanna think about him.
I'm not supposed to think about him.
But he's stuck in my head.
You're just in denial.
In denial?
You've always been like that.
You watch idol videos all the time
but say you're not a fan.
And you keep saving pictures
of that lead drama actor
but claim
it's because he's good at acting.
Do I do that?
Mmm… You do.
You're already head over heels for him
but you're trying to deny it.
Your words say otherwise, but
your heart is already racing toward him.
No, I can't.
I can't.
I can't! I shouldn't like him.
I simply can't!
I just can't.
Why? Huh?
Why can't you like the PE teacher?
[owl hooting]
Huh?
Why would you deny having a crush
on the PE teacher?
[intriguing music plays]
Oh…
No, that's not it.
No.
-Let's go?
-Huh?
Never mind what I said. Come on.
-Come on. Let's go.
-Hey.
-Hi.
Jenny, where are you going?
Oh, teachers' office.
I'm asking for permission
to go tour the city.
Good for you. Where are you going?
Oh. I'm going to go
to the Gyeongbokgung Palace in hanbok.
And then the market.
I'm going
to have gimbap and tteokbokki there.
Hongdae too. After Hongdae, I'm going
to the Han River to have ramyeon.
And then N Seoul Tower too.
Wow.
You've got that much energy
to go to all those places?
-Mm-hmm.
-Jenny,
you know you have to write
a field trip report afterwards, right?
Of course, I do.
"I have learned a lot
about Korean culture."
I just need to write it like that, right?
[chuckles] Bye!
She just… She has no idea
what the requirements are.
Let's just leave her be. She seems happy.
[sighs] Oh, boy.
THE DANCING CARNATION
NOTABLE WORK "MY MOTHER"
BY YOON DONG-JU
Wow.
You're reading that book again?
You must know all the lines.
[whispers] Yes, I do.
"The face, which no longer smiled,
was embracing a flower in full bloom."
If she no longer smiles, maybe
it means Dong-ju's mother passed away.
When he writes,
"And a small flower with no answer,"
it must mean that the small flower
is Dong-ju.
But why didn't he answer
when his mother called for him?
-Why didn't he look at her?
-[sighs]
He probably resented his mother.
[sobbing] I bet he probably regrets it
so much now.
Man,
you would've gotten a perfect score
on Korean lit if you studied like that.
How is the poem coming along?
Well…
Hey. [mouthing]
Hello.
[gentle music plays]
[somber music plays]
Go-ya.
Why didn't you come and talk to Mr. Yoon?
You've gotten really close.
What?
No, he gave me some feedback
about my poem.
I shouldn't like him, I simply can't.
I just can't.
That's why you shouldn't space out
when you walk.
His voice,
you could totally hear the concern
in his voice.
[chuckles]
WE WERE FRIENDS, EPISODE 6
[Young-hee] You're supposed to be
running this company someday. But now?
What is this I hear
about you and some guy?
Have you lost your mind?
Who told you that? Tell me!
I did. Ju Si-on.
It was all for your sake.
It was you?
Is this why you joined the company?
To win my mother's favor
and just tell her about Yoon and me?
[Da-ju scoffs]
Honestly, I did it for your future.
You're a man with a great future. [scoffs]
You can't afford to be the subject
of any gossip.
-Don't make me laugh.
-[chuckles]
Yoon is never gonna choose you,
even if you tear us apart.
He was the first
who laughed at my joke.
There's no way.
You see. Yoon laughed at all my jokes.
He probably just did it
so you wouldn't feel embarrassed.
Oh, no. Oh, no.
You don't get it.
The way Yoon looks at me is completely
different from the way he looks
at anyone else.
-It's the same.
-No, it's not.
-No…
You can take it out on me all you want.
But if you mess with him, I won't have it.
[scoffs]
-No, you're not going anywhere.
-Move.
No way. I'll never let you… [shrieks]
-Mr. Kim!
-[Kim] Yes, Madam Chairman!
Tie him up and don't let him go until you
handle Choi Yoon or whatever his name is.
-Get off me. Get off!
-[groans]
[groans]
[shouts]
[Young-hee] Get him!
[tires squealing]
[grunting]
[laughing]
[panting]
Are you okay?
This is why I told you never to be alone,
Choi Yoon!
Are you not hurt?
Let's go.
[gasps]
Oh! What am I doing?
[breathes shakily] Why…
Why did I turn into Yoon?
Why did I turn into Mr. Yoon?
It's so smooth. Why is it so vivid?
Could this be…
[playful music plays]
Oh.
TOPOLOGY OF ALGEBRAIC CURVES
AND SURFACES
HEY, IT'S BEEN A WHILE
I'M BACK IN KOREA
CAN WE MEET UP?
MURIM GIRLS' HIGH SCHOOL
[pensive music plays]
[no audible dialogue]
Okay.
Huh? Go-ya.
I need to talk to you.
What was that just now?
Oh. You mean that I told him I was
having trouble coming up with a title
for the poem.
So he said that I should try using
the first image that comes to mind
or a word that shows up a lot in the poem.
So I just asked him
to please check a few options for me.
And why did you go alone?
You could've invited me.
Well, I was going to. But I decided to go
alone because it wasn't a big deal.
"Not a big deal"?
I'm always too nervous to even
bring myself to say hello to Dong-ju.
But laughing and talking with him
is not a big deal to you?
[wistful music plays]
Oh, that's…
Be honest with me.
Mr. Jung's not your crush is he?
You have a crush on Dong-ju.
What are you talking about?
I know you do.
Otherwise, why would you go alone
to talk to him?
Why would you be in denial?
[sighs] No.
I wasn't talking about Mr. Yoon.
[sighs] Ah…
Why can't you just…
just say something to me then?
Anyone can see
you're acting suspicious right now.
[sighs]
Can't you trust me?
-What?
-Why can't you believe me.
I already said no.
Have I ever lied to you
about anything before?
[sighs]
Fine.
Let's go with that.
I'm just so blinded by a man that
I can't trust my innocent friend.
[sighs]
-It wouldn't be me, right? It wasn't…
-It was me. I did it.
Did you get choco balls?
Whatever.
Hey.
What's wrong with her?
-You think they had a fight?
-They definitely had a fight.
I think so.
-[Dan-ji] Geez.
-It's so weird.
[sighs]
[grunts]
[somber music plays]
I hope she won't be angry too long.
[sighs]
CHAPTER 31:
EVERYONE HAS A SPECIAL SOMEONE
[sniffs]
Oh.
What the heck?
Why am I waiting for Math
when Mr. Jung walked out of his house?
[gasps]
Oh, no.
When I look at his face, it feels…
Are you okay?
[gasps]
[grunts]
No way.
[Go-ya] Love is like first snow.
Right in that moment.
When you see them…
Oh! And you know they're the one.
It always comes when you least expect it.
MINI MOCK EXAMINATION 7
[Eui-Ju] My first love.
My first love is Math and not PE?
What do I do?
What do I do? What do I do?
[phone buzzes]
[barista] Your large mocha's ready.
Thank you. Enjoy your coffee.
Thank you very much.
[sighs]
Oh.
[chuckles]
What the heck?
What is he doing here?
[gasps]
Why didn't I see him earlier?
Hold on.
When I ordered this,
I was up at the counter.
[chuckles] Oh man. [laughs]
Wait. Uh… Hold on.
Did he know I was here,
that I like this place?
Oh, my…
[clears throat] Maybe not.
Is this what people call destiny?
[chuckles]
What's that?
Is that a mocha?
[gasps]
-[Woo-su chuckles]
-[chuckles] It's so not like him.
And he added so much whipped cream on top.
Oh, please. It looks just like mine.
What's with him?
Huh? Why is he waving his hand?
[door opens]
[person chuckles]
[wistful music plays]
Been a while.
-I've missed you so much.
-[both chuckle]
[Eui-ju] I really didn't know
what to make of my feelings.
But then
it all became very clear.
What those reckless, aimless feelings
of mine had really been all along.
Everyone has someone like that,
at least once,
someone who can make
your heart suddenly drop.