(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
[rock music playing]
CHAPTER 32:
A VARIABLE CALLED NA DEUL-I
-Everything going well?
-Mm-hmm.
[gentle pop music playing on speaker]
It's nice to see you're doing well too.
[chuckles]
Honestly I was a little surprised
to hear from you,
but glad too.
Really, then
why didn't you reach out to me first?
[chuckles]
Are you okay now?
Mmm.
I was so worried
when I heard about your surgery.
I couldn't contact you.
I'm sorry I didn't tell you.
I was just as shocked myself.
And I was frustrated.
So, you decided to become a teacher?
That was unexpected.
I thought you'd obviously continue
with the research.
[no audible dialogue]
[slow, gentle music playing]
[both chuckling]
-What is it?
-What?
[both chuckle]
[E-den] Eui-ju?
What are you doing here?
EPISODE 10
Mr. Ha.
[stuttering] I just came here to study,
[chuckles] But I'm going to go home now.
Eui-ju.
You finally decided to start studying?
[laughs]
[chuckling] And how come you're here?
-Is that Mr. Ga?
-[Eui-ju whispering] No, wait.
Look who's here!
The cold- blooded robot,
Mr. Ga, is having coffee with someone,
and a lady at that!
[stammers] Hold on.
Are you…
Professor Na Deul-i? Is that right?
Uh…
-Yes.
-[gasps, laughs]
Oh, my! I knew it! I saw you on the news.
I was really impressed by your interview
about winning the Fields Medal.
[Deul-i] Oh, thank you so much.
Oops, I'm sorry, my bad.
Hello. I'm Mr. Ga's colleague at school.
My name is Ha E-den.
It's so very nice to meet you.
I see.
Oh.
[chuckles]
Anyway, I was just wondering, what exactly
is your relationship with Mr. Ga Woo-su?
-We're friends.
-Oh, yeah?
So you're just friends? I see.
But you're alone together
at this coffee shop.
That seems like a date to me. [chuckles]
Should we go?
-[chuckles]
-Let's go.
[sighs] The two of you make
such a lovely couple.
Like a match made in heaven.
See you soon.
-[stutters] Goodbye.
-Goodbye.
Keep studying, all right?
If you want to become someone
like Professor Na Deul-i.
Take care now.
-[Woo-su] Allow me.
-[door opens]
[Deul-i] Oh. Okay. Thank you.
Hello there.
Uh… My name is Yeo Eui-ju,
and Mr. Ga Woo-su is actually
my homeroom teacher at school.
Oh. Hello there.
Whoa. It's such a surprise to see that
you have a student of your own.
[chuckles]
Are you his friend
from when you were in college?
Oh, no.
We've been friends since middle school.
Ah… Middle school.
That's a long time.
You can go now.
Remember what I offered.
You'll consider it?
I'm not sure.
Oh. Are you playing hard to get?
[chuckles] Just get going now.
All right.
Oh. I'll see you again
another time, Eui-ju.
Yes. Goodbye now.
Bye.
-Mr. Ga, your friend…
-[sighs]
…she seems like a really wonderful person.
She's beautiful
and she seems really kind too.
And to have even won a Fields Medal.
Wow. That's seriously amazing, really.
I wish I had a friend like that.
I bet she's incredibly popular too.
She probably has a boyfriend.
[sighs] But also, it could be tiring
to be around someone that perfect.
You know,
when someone's good at everything,
the people around them tend
to get compared.
It can make them feel small for no reason.
So what's your point?
I mean, I was just wondering
what kind of boyfriend
someone that gorgeous might have.
Why are you wondering?
If you don't get over a 50
on the upcoming math exam,
I'll tell your parents about your novel
during the parent-teacher meeting.
Huh?
Hey, no, that's unfair!
Mr. Ga, you don't mean it, do you?
Do you? You shouldn't…
Come on, Mr. Ga.
I'll try my best.
But I may not be able to get a 50.
Mr. Ga, about what your friend
was talking about earlier…
[clears throat]
What did she ask you to consider?
It's none of your business.
Would it kill him
to say it a little nicer?
[phone buzzes]
Remember my soda.
Mr. Ga, wait a second.
H-Hold on, wait there.
Oh, no. Don't go, don't go, don't go.
Uh… Just wait right there.
I'll be right back.
-[whimsical music playing]
-Hey, hey.
I'm all done. [chuckles]
Drinking soda is a common cause
of constipation.
Hope you won't have to go to the ER again.
I didn't buy it for me.
I had to buy it for my younger brother.
What a sister.
[chuckles] He just uses me
because he has dirt on me.
-[sniffs]
-What does he have on you?
You see. [sighs] It's just that
I only got caught by two people.
That day,
I was lost in my writing again as usual.
And I was also chatting online.
[whimsical music playing]
[online friend 1] I was just wondering
under what name
you've all saved this group chat.
[online friend 2] Beautiful Life. BL.
[online friend 3] How about
a real estate group chat?
Since my husband
checks my phone sometimes.
[Eui-ju] This is a draft
of what I'm working on these days.
It's about a young master and his servant.
I'd appreciate your feedback on this.
[online friend 1]
I love the relationship setting.
[online friend 2] I wonder why
your novels don't get many views.
I feel frustrated myself.
[Eui-ju] A sweet young master bawling
because of a feisty servant.
[sighs] Just thinking about it
is thrilling.
[door creaks]
[music stops]
[Eui-ju] I think
there's someone
behind me right now.
Could it be a ghost?
[online friend 1]
You'll be happy if it's a ghost.
If it's your parents,
my heart goes out to you.
[tense music playing]
[exhales heavily]
-[tapping keys]
-[owl hooting]
[thunder rumbles]
[thunderclap]
Did you see it?
Well, at least,
I'm glad it wasn't my mom or my dad.
But I do have to keep buying him soda
whenever he wants me to.
-[sighs]
-Why do you like it so much?
I don't know.
I just like it. That's all.
That's probably why
you're still going at it.
Well, somehow I still feel like
I'll make it big one day.
So you have baseless confidence.
If your confidence has a basis,
that's not confidence, it's a prediction.
[gasps] That means
I'm going to keep moving forward.
And I'll keep getting better.
Mr. Ga.
Remember, when EBC came
to film the TV show,
and you stopped
right in the middle of telling your story?
[clears throat]
I still want to know why
you decided to become a teacher.
[people talking on television]
So did you have a good time?
Yeah.
[groans]
She came back to Korea after years
of glory for having won a Fields Medal.
But she came all the way to Jeonju
just to see you?
Huh? Why?
And it wasn't like
she wanted to see the whole Olympiad crew.
It was just you.
Only you.
Why only you?
I guess beautiful memories sprouted
from a fragment of your summer-like youth.
-[Gi-jeon] Did they go out together?
-[Da-ju] Mmm!
There really is
no other explanation for it.
For things to be like that,
there has to be chemistry
between a man and a woman.
That spark is
what makes you remember someone
for years
and makes you want to see them again.
-Comprendes, amigo?
-[Gi-jeon] Right.
It's none of your business.
-Guess it's true.
-[door closes]
That bastard wasn't just studying
after all. [clicks tongue]
The way I see it, that girl Na Deul-i and
Woo-su met at the Olympiad,
dated, and then they just broke up.
-No way.
-Mm-hmm.
That's why he dropped out
in the middle of it all. Why?
Just to go see his ex-girlfriend again,
his heart…
-Mm-mmm…
-His heart.
He felt too restless and uneasy.
That's why he couldn't keep going.
The cold-blooded Ga Woo-su had
a flicker of love.
-[sighs] Dang.
-You know what I'm saying?
-Yeah, that's my boy. [clicks tongue]
-Come on. That can't be the reason.
It sure can be.
Why? Because they were rivals.
Woo-su must've gone, like…
"I'll give up here.
You can go higher or whatever if you want.
Only one of us can win."
So you're saying Woo-su gave up
on math over a girl he liked? No way.
Actually,
there's another reason.
What is it?
You know,
his camera phobia.
He gave up in case he won.
-Mmm…
-Ah…
[scoffs]
[imitates Deul-i] "Wow.
It's such a surprise
to see that
you have a student of your own.
[scoffs]
[normal voice]
Why is it such a surprise? Huh?
Is it that surprising for a teacher
to have a student?
I'll see you again another time, Eui-ju.
"Another time"?
[scoffs]
That's right.
We may meet again sometime.
[clears throat]
-[whimsical music playing]
-[sighs]
[dramatic sting plays]
WE WERE FRIENDS, EPISODE 7
[Dong-ju coughing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[rope grinding, creaking]
Who are you?
Me?
The Chair's secretary, Na Ran-i.
As long as I'm getting paid, I'll do
anything, even dirty work like this.
[sinister music playing]
I was ordered to get you away
from Ju Si-on.
Your face is too handsome to be wasted.
[chuckles]
But I need you gone.
-Don't do it! Don't!
-[grunts]
-[groans]
[door bangs]
[western music playing]
Choi Yoon!
[gasps] How did you find us?
[breathes heavily, grunts]
[grunts]
-[Deul-i grunts]
-[grunts]
[grunting]
[yells]
-[grunts]
-[Woo-su grunts]
[groans]
[pants]
-[Deul-i grunts]
-Choi Yoon!
Are you okay?
Yes, I'm okay.
SI-ON LOWERED HIMSELF
TO MEET YOON'S EYES
Let's go.
SO CLOSE AND SO INTENSE,
HIS GAZE MADE YOON'S HEART RACE
JUST THEN, RAN-I CALLED OUT
[Deul-i] This is amusing.
We'll see how long
you can keep this whole thing going.
RAN-I'S COMMENT
PROVOKED YOON'S WILDER NATURE
Hold on.
I don't leave debts unpaid.
[Deul-i] No!
No! Don't do it!
YOON BID HER FAREWELL
IT WAS FOR SI-ON, OF ALL PEOPLE
[sighs]
CHAPTER 33:
SOMETHING UTTERLY USELESS
-[Woo-su] Eun Ha-su.
-Here.
-[Woo-su] Oh A-rin.
-[Woo-su] Choi Yu-mi.
-Here.
-[Woo-su] Yeo Eui-ju.
-Choi Go-ya.
-Here.
Choi Ji-a.
-Hong Su-min.
-Here.
-[Woo-su] Jeon Chae-won.
-[Woo-su] Im Su-yeon.
-Here.
-Im Su-yeon.
-[Woo-su] Lee Eun-ji.
-Here.
-[Woo-su] Choi Hye-jeong.
Are you ready for today's class?
[students murmuring]
Why does it smell like alcohol?
Do you smell that?
-[tense music playing]
-It smells so nasty.
It kinda smells like alcohol.
-[pounds]
-Quiet down.
Who is on cleaning duty?
[Eui-ju] M-Me.
-Yeo Eui-ju.
-Yes?
-Do it again.
-Sure.
Let some air in. Open the windows.
-[students murmuring]
-[student grunts] It's cold.
Why? Is he for real?
Choi Ji-a, go see the nurse.
[students whispering]
-Hi.
-Hello.
[sniffing]
Hey!
Mr. Ga Woo-su.
She's your student, right?
Are you aware that
she came to school completely drunk?
[Young-hee] Outrageous!
Totally outrageous.
How could a student come to school
reeking of alcohol like this, huh?
[retches]
[E-den, Young-hee scoff]
Aren't you the one
who didn't wear a school uniform
during the EBC production?
Do you even plan
to keep going to school at all, dear?
Please, Ms. Kim.
Let me talk to her and find out exactly
what happened, and I'll get back to you.
Mr. Ga Woo-su.
Is there any reason whatsoever
I should tolerate underage drinking here?
Wait outside.
-[tuts]
-[door closes]
I don't wanna argue
over something trivial.
[groans]
I got a massage yesterday.
-[E-den] Aw…
-My shoulders are stiff again.
[groans]
Choi Ji-a has different circumstances
from those of other students.
Without parental care,
she lives in a foster shelter,
working to support herself.
Even after all that, she's still willing
to come to school almost every day.
Oh, really?
That's great.
She'll be able to manage
at another school then. Hmm?
She might look tough
but she's still just a kid.
As her homeroom teacher,
I'll take responsibility
and I'll make sure
you see real change in Choi Ji-a.
Please just give her chance.
Mr. Ga Woo-su.
Do you know what our school motto is?
Be an Elite! That's what it is.
No matter how you look at it, whatever
that student plans to do with her life…
[sighs] …it's a far cry from that.
And no matter how much I think of it,
she just doesn't belong
at Murim Girls' High School. That's all.
You may go now.
[sighs]
-[door closes]
-[E-den scoffs]
Who does he think he is,
taking the wrong side?
How could he possibly stand up for a kid
who came to school drunk?
[scoffs] So annoying.
Would you believe
he's friends with the Na Deul-i?
Who's Na Deul-i?
Auntie, really? You're kidding.
She's the professor
who won the Fields Medal.
They're friends.
What?
I can't believe what you're saying!
Why are you telling me this now?
When was I supposed to tell you?
-[scoffs]
-[Young-hee exclaims]
Choi Ji-a.
Why did you…
It's wrong for a student
to show up drunk at school.
What matters here is
what you choose to do next.
Write a detailed paper self-reflecting
on what exactly you did wrong
and how you're going to change.
I'm going to hand it to the principal.
Okay.
I'll try to reduce the penalty, so
don't forget to wear your school uniform.
And no more absences.
Okay.
-[Yeong-jae] This is the best.
-[Dan-ji] What on earth is this?
-Hey, Eui-ju. Over here. Come on.
-Eui-ju, come!
-Hurry. Over here.
-That was so cool.
-Whoa, this is to die for.
-Try this.
This lunch is so delicious.
Go-ya, where are you going?
Can I eat here with you?
Eui-ju, sit down. Sit.
[Dan-ji] Let's…
[student] Here. Have some of my soup.
[Yeong-jae] Oh. The meat is
so delicious today. Try this too.
Eat up, Eui-ju. It's so good.
Go-ya, can I talk to you for a sec…
[student] I don't know.
I left them in my locker.
[student 2] Yeah. The exam is coming soon.
Where are you going? Huh?
No, I get it.
-Guys, guys I have crazy news.
-What is it?
Guess what.
Young-hee was going to transfer Ji-a.
But Mr. Ga stopped her.
-Really?
-No way.
She's on probation.
Hmm. I wonder what kind of card he played.
I bet there's something.
Anyway, when are you going
to make up with Go-ya?
You keep making me
tell the same story twice. [smacks lips]
What a mess, huh?
Um…
Does she still refuse to talk to you?
Mm-hmm.
Well then what did you guys fight about?
We didn't.
W-We didn't fight.
-[Dan-ji] What is it?
-[Yeong-jae] As if.
-[Dan-ji] Come on. Tell us.
-I don't believe you.
[crickets chirping]
[Deul-i] I'm looking to do
some joint research with you.
[gentle music playing]
It's been really nice talking to you.
[chuckles]
I'm not sure how long it will take
but I'd really like to study it with you.
The topology of algebraic curves
and surfaces.
Why that topic?
I don't know. I was just drawn to it.
When looking for something that
is never useful.
It reminded me of a quote
by the British mathematician Hardy.
"None of my discoveries has made,
or is likely to make,
any difference
to the comfort of the world,
directly or indirectly.
-For better or worse…
-"…or worse,
[both] I have never done anything useful."
[both chuckle]
I want to try that.
Accomplishing something utterly useless.
[sighs]
Where are you going?
For a walk.
I'll come with.
I need to go for a walk too.
Are you still getting headaches?
Sometimes.
Shouldn't you see the doctor?
It's not that bad.
[Dong-ju] Still, go for a checkup.
It's better to be safe than sorry.
[Woo-su] Okay.
[Dong-ju] Don't just say it, though.
Make sure you go.
[Woo-su] Okay.
[sighs]
[smacks lips, sighs]
[laptop chimes]
I need a soda.
[sighs]
But I'm already home!
-[sighs]
-[typing]
I'm in my room already.
Can't you wait until tomorrow?
Mom! I have something to tell you.
Hey, hey, hey, Eui-do.
Okay, fine. [laughs] Okay, fine.
I'll go, I'll go.
[sighs]
[pop music playing on speakers]
What do you think
about your friend's offer?
Na Deul-i's?
Honestly.
Not interested at all.
That's a lie.
You answered that way too fast.
Like it was planned.
You know, I want you to spend your time
on something that you really want to do.
So when you have a chance,
go to the States.
And do the research you want
before it's too late.
[Eui-ju] You're going to the States,
Mr. Ga?
[somber music playing]
-[Woo-su] It's late. Go home.
-No.
The truth is, I…
[Woo-su] Didn't I tell you
to stay away from her?
[Dong-ju groans] Now what?
-[Woo-su] How did you get here?
-[Eui-ju] Mr. Ga. What do I do?
[grunts] Why wouldn't she pick up?
Why is she not even checking her phone?
-[Ji-a] Get out of here.
-[gasps] Mr. Ga!
[Woo-su] I guess
you guys haven't figured me out yet.
[Eui-ju] You'll be dead meat
for real, then.
Dang. He's so cool.
So cool.
[Go-ya] Just tell him.
You have to look into his eyes
to show you mean it.
-I…
-[Go-ya] Make eye contact.
For at least three seconds.