(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
Kim!
..have we ever met each other?
Why...
do I draw your portrait.
You remember me?
These days, Tao Sor seems to want to remember things a lot more.
Tao Sor remembering isn't an easy thing, you know?
This picture... is the first one you drew.
I don't have to introduce myself, right?
Everyone remembers me...
but I can't remember anyone.
He has to be exposed to the same situation for a good length of time
I'm Bruce. Nice to meet you.
I'm Peter.
And what about people?
This... I'm not so sure about.
He just brought some people to learn cooking.
You don't know each other.
I think...
I should leave.
Hey, you!
Where are you running off to?
Startled?
Why would you...
do that to me?
I'm just...
doing what I feel like doing.
I'm the one...
that'll be your memory.
Chef Mochi..
Why do you look so out of it tomay?
Wait! Out of it today?
Do I really look like that?
I dunno, I'm just playing around!
You're worried about teaching today, right?
It's not that..
- Huh? Then what is it?
I'm not sure either.
Hmm...
Don't be worried, Chef Mochi.
This isn't your first time, you'll figure it out.
But either way, just prep your station for the time being.
Looks like there's a few things missing
I'll go get the rest.
Tao Sor!
What are we going to make today, Chef?
Pom Poms for sure!
What you mean, pom poms? It's Wontons!
I've brought these two to learn with you before, Mangmo and Future.
The clip we posted last time got a ton of hits!
Hey, the view over there's nice!
Should we go take some inserts?
Alright!
- Let's go!
I'm Kim.
Do you need me to help with anything?
Have we ever met before?
We made a promise to each other.
Do you remember anything?
Promise?
When?
Yesterday!
I promised you...
that I would be your memory.
I'm the one that will be your memory.
Why...
did you say exactly what I heard in my dreams?
Sometimes...
these things aren't just from your dreams.
I...
am your yesterday.
The two of us...
kissed.
Oh!
Our students have arrived!
Shall we get started, Chef Mochi?
OK
Nice view, don't you think?
Sure.
It is a nice view, but..
I think, if it was renovated to look more modern...
you could bring in more tourists, for example young folks and so newer.
I like the same old things
not a fan of change.
The Treasure Resort is like this
and that's how people remember it
if..
Then...
if there's nothing, I'll excuse myself
I think you...
should go do your job properly.
Although I know how you feel about Tao Sor
I'll have to warn you a second time.
Quit messing with Tao Sor's life.
This situation is far more delicate and complicated than you think.
Hello, we're from Siam Sea. Could we invite you to come promote our yachts?
Doesn't look professional at all...
To Miss Nao. I - a representative of Siam Sea, am inviting you to be a part of our yacht business promotional campaign.
If you have any interest, we are happy to provide more details.
Now I look like a scammer.
Just send it!
I'm interested. When? Tomorrow?
We can do tomorrow. Please give me a copy of your ID, I will get you a ticket.
Are you for real?
Too fast?
We could do some other day.
- No, tomorrow's fine.
Hm? You don't have class today?
Sis, I got an influencer to come shoot content for us. See? What do you think.
Don't spend too much!
It's gonna be monsoon season soon, can't do much for sales.
Sis, just wait and see.
This will be a new thing.
If a famous fortune teller does readings on our boats,
Our boats are gonna get huge!
People will hoard to us, right?
Feeling like they're absorbing energy from nature itself.
Alright, whatever.
But when are they coming?
Tomorrow!
Tomorrow...
Tomorrow?!!
You crazy?
You just told me!
What are you doing?
Didn't you say so yourself? Monsoon season's coming, people aren't gonna come.
Alright, alright!
Just don't use the bigger ones, it's a waste of fuel.
Ok... Dad. I'm outta here!
And where are you off to now?
- Central!
About what you said yesterday, that we...
Kissed?
Did we really kiss?
Then that means that we're a couple, right?
And, and..
Does Talay know about this?
I don't think he does. Because if he did, he would've told me...
Who exactly are you?
I already told you
that I'll be your memory for you.
Prove it! A picture or something that says we're a couple.
So, the thing is...
we're not exactly at that point yet, but..
Or if you still don't believe me,
should we try this?
Tao Sor!
Excuse me...
Hello?
Is that... a picture I drew?
Of course!
You were drawing me on the beach while I was surfing
and I saw you.
So I walked straight up to you.
From there, we talked a little
and you gave me this picture.
You signed your name on the top corner as well.
After that, I invited you to come surf with me.
But you were afraid of the ocean.
You know that much about me?
Then...
how did we end up kissing?
Well, yesterday...
we went to an aquarium together.
After that, we just walked around for a bit
after that...
the atmosphere just led me to...
kiss you.
I have to apologize for that, Tao Sor.
For... not asking for your consent.
Forget it.
I...
wouldn't remember anyway.
That's all.
- Oh!
Hold on a moment, Tao Sor.
In that case...
let's get to know each other better
could we?
My name is Tao Sor.
I like cooking.
I'm afraid of the ocean.
As for me,
my name is Kim
I'm from Bangkok
I had to come to my hometown of Phuket
for a period of 1 year.
Because my mother was told by a Feng Shui master that I have to fix my year of bad fortune here.
And... when you surf, how does it feel?
It makes me feel like...
I fall nto a world with no noise
no people,
nothing at all...
except the waves that hit my body.
Really? What else is there?
The water hits us,
But we have to understand the timing.
Kind of like trying to speak to it.
The stronger the waves,
the more fun it is, making me feel even more alive.
It's like flying, Tao Sor.
It's.. not just a sport.
But...
It's like freedom.
We just have to go with the flow and that's enough.
Thank you.
If you really are my memory.
Could you help writing down
that I want to try doing it once.
Thank you as well.
I hope...
you'll be able to remember me, Tao Sor.
Sweet dreams, Kim. I hope I'll be able to remeber you tomorrow.
Sweet dreams. Have a good night.
Thank you, Kim.
You better remember me, Tao Sor!
Hello? Where are you? I'm waiting at the parking lot.
I'm actually getting coffee, please wait a moment.
Should I go to you?
- Nao!
I'm over here!
I'm sorry, I didn't remember that you were SilvyStar.
You know my channel too?
Probably a lot more than you think I do.
Shall we get going?
Okay.
Shall we go?
Happy holidays, everyone! Today I'm aboard a luxurious boat from Siam Sea, in order to take in some fresh, natural energy!
It's said that celebs and idols like travelling to different places to absorb different energies.
"Nao is so pretty.."
Thank you so much, Aod! Don't forget to find time to take in some postive energy like this!
"I want to get my fortune told too!"
I'm in Phuket at the moment. If you could fly over here, I'll be glad to make an appointment!
Alright, we're reached an important section of our time here, after absorbing some positive energy.
Let's see just how accurate we can get.
Does anyone want to try?
Go on!
Are my cards really that bad?
Honestly, yes. They're not very good, both your career and love life.
Looks like you won't reach your goals..
What you desire, you might not get. What you don't, you wouldn't get anyways.
But..it's okay! Since we're on a boat absorbing some good manna, it'll get better soon!
In that case, do you want to continue your stream?
- Okay!
Oh, I'm sorry!
- Be careful, it's hot!
I got this for you.
- Thank you!
Be careful, it's really hot!
- Okay.
Are you taking photos? I can take them for you.
- Yes!
That'll be great, thank you!
Here! I wanna get this angle here.
- Oh, okay.
Gorgeous!
You wanna take one together?
- Hm? Together?
- Yes.
How should we...
- I'll do it.
Which spot's good? Over here?
1, 2, 3!
Someone asked what we'll do after we're done?
I wanna visit so many places because I've never been here, but...
I'm still not sure where to go.
Oh, there's only a few photos?
Oh. Sorry, Nao. My hands were shaking alot,
so I couldn't take a lot.
Want some more? I'll take them for you.
It's okay.
Yeah, why did you have me come promote your family's business?
Because...
Because I like you.
Are my cards really that bad?
Honestly, yes. They're not very good, both your career and love life.
Looks like you won't reach your goals..
What you desire, you might not get. What you don't, you wouldn't get anyways.
Actually, you seem to be pretty famous
and it could bring in a lot of clients
I decided to contact you.
Nao, what's wrong? Are you OK?
Are there any cafes are restaurants nearby?
Cafe?
Well, yeah.
Can you take me there?
Right now?
Yeah!
Okay..
Alright? Let's go!
I'll take you there.
Khun Im asked where I am,
right now I'm at Methee Phuket.
Alright, let's take a look, shall we?
Khun Auey asked about love.
What your love life is gonna be like...
Alright, this is the first card.
Ah, you will meet a good looking one.
A handsome one, that will make your heart full and satisified.
But, you might have to go through some hardships, and it might be tiring.
You'll have to fight by yourself a lot.
But I'm not sure why, but the cards say you'll have to fight...
Let's have another card for explanation.
The cards say you have to meditate.
That is your antidote.
Let's dive deeper.
Wow, there will be a woman to help with your relationships.
Let's look at another card.
Everyone, please excuse me.
Let me find some new energires to absorb.
I'll be back.
We have to go?
Yes. You've packed already, right?
Yeah, but I have a lot viewers right now...
How bout this? You can continue the stream on the car, so you won't miss your flight. Okay?
- Yes!
Then can you hurry up? It's..
- Okay, okay, okay...
Thank you to everyone who tuned in, I'll see you guys in Bangkok soon! Bye bye!
We're here, right? Thanks!
I think we're too late, Nao...
Huh?
The plane's already left.
But it's okay. I'll buy you a new ticket.
It's my fault, I'm really sorry.
It's fine! Since we missed the flight, can we change
from a plane ticket into a hotel?
Then... I'll take you to a resort that my family's a partner with, okay?
Okay..
I'm really sorry, okay?
It's really fine!
Let's go, Tao Sor!
It's late, let's go home.
Can I...
stay a bit longer?
Of course!
You can stay as long as you need to.
My brother's calling?
Can I talk to him?
Hello, Kim? Is Tao Sor with you?
Tai...
Tao Sor.
What are you doing with him?
Where are you now? I'll pick you up.
Can I see the views at the pier first? And when I'm done, I'll come back myself.
I'll take you tomorrow, it's late now.
And, how will I know that you'll take me there tomorrow?
Hey, you're...
okay, right?
I'm okay.
Right now... I want to do what I want to do.
Before I forget everything.
It's funny, right?
To... wake up and not know who you are.
Not knowing what to do,
who to go out with,
or even...
who you're friends with.
It'd be nice if I could remember just a little bit of yesterday.
In that case, I...
Mr. Today's Memories,
am happy to serve!
Then, can you remember this for me?
Yes, sir!
What the hell did you do to my brother, you asshole?!
Do what?!
We gave each other consent!
You tricked him here, didn't you?
You're so heartless!
I didn't trick your brother here.
How about you? How are you taking care of him when you let me take him out here?
Oh, you little...
How can you say that?!
From now on, I ask to decline all clients from Siam Sea.
Why? What happened?
Let's just say...
I don't want to continue.
I don't need Kim at my resort.
I ask for my family's safety first.
Me and Tao Sor were consentual to each other.
You..
- I love Tao Sor!
He loves me?
Let Tao Sor forget that feeling along with you!
I've proven to Tao Sor,
that I'll be his memory for him!
Your luck in love looks really good.
Really?
They said they'll be medium to help you achieve your goals.
Medium... like...
Cupid or something?
Yes!