(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
Don't screw with me.
Why did you just go and die on your own?
If you're going to die,
tell us everything first.
Someone related to him
might know something.
There must be a clue somewhere.
Is it a phone number?
Hello.
Who is this?
Why are you picking up, Fumi…
BREATHING MOUNTAINS
FUMI KARASHIMA PHOTO EXHIBIT
Wait,
are you Makoto?
Yes.
There’s something I want to ask.
Can we meet somewhere?
Why are those two connected?
We'll have to ask her directly.
Maybe she even knows Tsuda’s motive.
Is that key the only clue left?
Hand it over.
What you just put in your pocket.
The Violent Crimes Division will keep that
until the bereaved family is located.
Take it without permission and
you'll be subject to disciplinary action.
Don't do it.
Searching any further is useless.
Tsuda
didn't kill your parents.
What?
How do you know that?
I never thought you brothers
would end up becoming police officers.
I used to be in the prefectural
police's First Division.
First Division?
No way…
I was chasing that case.
When will you catch them?
Why did my mom and dad die?
You two were young back then.
It's no wonder you didn't notice.
Did you catch the killer?
I looked into it,
but it wasn't that person.
What?
But we, the police,
will definitely catch the culprit.
That night,
Tsuda was called out
by someone from a publishing company
and was drinking at a pub in Jimbocho.
Maybe he faked an alibi?
He said he would come
to our house that night.
He was caught on a security camera.
But the records back then
didn't mention it…
A politician the Second Division
was tailing also appeared in that footage.
To prevent it from leaking,
the higher-ups decided not to report it
and just kept it an internal issue.
I never imagined you guys
were still chasing Tsuda.
If that's the case, why did he run away?
If he’s innocent,
he had no need to disappear.
He was removed from the list of suspects.
You know the police
didn't look further into him.
Is there anything else
you know about Tsuda?
Mr. Koike!
Tsuda
might have been interviewing
people other than your father.
Other people?
The factory where the fire happened.
1995, APRIL 26
Apparently, he was sniffing
around that area.
I don't think it is relevant
to the case, though.
Give it.
The key.
-Help us out here.
-What?
If there's a similar key,
they won't notice.
What are you guys--
At least do that much for us.
Since you didn't do anything
for us back then.
The statute of limitations expired.
What’s the point
of finding the culprit now?
We want to know.
Why were our parents killed?
We won't cause you any more trouble.
LAND FOR LEASE AS CAR PARK, STORAGE, ETC.
If he was investigating the factory,
that explains why he knows Fumi.
What was Tsuda investigating?
Seems after the fire,
the land here was sold off.
But it’s not like everything is gone.
If it’s not Tsuda,
the culprit is still out there somewhere.
I'm Kawano from the Akita Police.
Please, go ahead.
Let’s get started then.
Resident Aiko Mizusawa
was killed in an arson-murder
at her apartment in the Kanagawa Ward.
Gold bars worth 100 million yen
were found in the residence.
After verification,
they matched the gold bars
from the 400 million yen robbery
that occurred in Akita a year ago.
There were four robbers.
Was Aiko Mizusawa's name
on the suspect list?
No, she wasn't listed here.
There's testimony that before her death,
Mizusawa was being stalked
by a man named Togo.
He is thought to be either
one of the robbers, or the mastermind.
Do you have any information on him?
We have no information at this time.
Are you saying that
this Togo man is the arsonist?
No, the one who set the fire
is likely Yugo Hiranaka.
Yugo Hiranaka?
Flyers used to start the fire
were only distributed around
where Hiranaka lives.
Hiranaka also had a bruise on his neck
that closely resembled the tattoo
of one of the four robbers.
Hiranaka and Togo might have been
chasing Mizusawa together.
However, Hiranaka fled by car.
We are currently tracking him.
Did Hiranaka flee in a panic?
His smartphone is turned off, right?
Yes.
It’s difficult to pinpoint his location
via cell signal.
He lives in a nice house.
Yes.
Right.
Do you think he left and met up with Togo?
They’re probably overseas by now.
Such shallow logic.
-What?
-Oh, no.
-What did you just say?
-That hurts.
-I'm sorry.
-Hey.
Hey.
They found
Yugo Hiranaka's body.
What?
One, two, three.
There.
-Scale.
-Here.
Nine stab wounds were confirmed
on the back of the body.
The fatal wound was a stab
below the right shoulder blade.
The blade pierced the lungs,
causing air and blood to fill the chest.
The culprit must have had a strong grudge.
Dr. Kagura.
There’s a variation
in the depth of the wounds.
They range from six centimeters
to 14 centimeters at the deepest.
What about the angle?
The blade was inserted like this…
Almost vertically.
I see.
What’s bothering you?
The force of the stabs.
If there’s a strong intent to kill,
the blade is usually plunged in deep.
But the body had several
shallow wounds as well.
-In cases like this…
-They were probably in a hurry.
Maybe someone was coming.
Repeated stabbing in a short time?
Repeated stabbing would cause
the depth of the wounds to vary.
The man killed at the marina
is Yugo Hiranaka, 23 years old.
An investor who owns several
properties within the prefecture.
His legal residence was Akita Prefecture,
the same as Aiko Mizusawa.
Hiranaka suffered neglect as a child
and was reportedly estranged
from his parents.
This photo was found at his home.
It also shows Aiko Mizusawa
and a person believed
to be her friend, Saki Yokokura.
Hiranaka started investing one year ago,
immediately after the gold robbery.
Like Aiko Mizusawa,
Hiranaka may have used
the gold bars he made off with.
The autopsy results?
On Yugo Hiranaka's body,
we found no defensive wounds.
Does that mean he knew the suspect?
We don't know that yet.
The moment of the crime
was not caught on security cameras,
but a person carrying a suitcase
was sighted near the marina
at the same time.
Is this man Togo?
The motive for the crime
was likely the suitcase.
The case the man is holding
belonged to Hiranaka.
The contents might be
the rest of the gold bars.
It's possible they had
a falling out, and he took it.
The robbers were a group of four.
It's hard to believe
it’s just a coincidence.
It's possible this Yuzuru boy's
family name is Togo.
Continue to search for witnesses, and…
investigate Saki Yokokura
as a person of interest.
Yes, sir!
BATHHOUSE
This place hasn't changed.
Man, I'm hungry.
But…
I just don't get it.
Get what?
Why Hiranaka
went as far as to set fire to the house
of his childhood friend, Aiko Mizusawa.
Hey.
I'm off the clock right now.
Maybe he was told to kill her, to be
forgiven for running off with the gold.
I just felt refreshed,
don't bring up such heavy topics.
And then he was betrayed
and killed by Togo.
Did the gold bars destroy the relationship
the four of them had?
We just have to find
one of the people in that photo.
What about Saki Yokokura?
She vanished.
When First Division went, the room
was ransacked, and bloodstains were found.
-Check the security cameras.
-Yes.
That might be Togo's doing as well.
Did he kidnap her
to find out where the gold is?
It's too early to be certain,
but you should hurry up and go.
What?
To Akita.
What a pain.
Mogi, gyoza.
For two.
What happened to the man named Tsuda?
He died of an illness.
We didn't get
any info out of him in the end.
I see.
But…
it's not over yet.
Minoru.
I'll leave it to you.
Sure.
KARASHIMA
Welcome.
It has been a while.
Minoru?
Here you go.
Makoto had to go to Akita
on a sudden business trip.
I see. Sounds like he's doing well.
Fumi, how have you been since then?
I underwent surgery,
and steadily continued with my rehab…
Is that how you're able to take
photos of mountains again?
I'm still full of energy, you know.
I'm going climbing again next week.
Back then,
I had almost given up,
thinking it was impossible.
It’s amazing that you’re even holding
a solo exhibition now.
Oh, you know a lot.
I looked you up online.
So, what is it today?
You wanted to ask me something?
You know a man
named Yuji Tsuda, don't you?
Tsuda?
He used to write nonfiction books.
An author.
YUJI TSUDA
VOICES OF THE DEAD
I don't know anyone like that.
But he had your number, Fumi.
Mine?
Before the incident,
did this man ever visit you?
I'm sorry.
Back then, I avoided meeting people.
It's nice to see you again.
Darling, this is Minoru.
You know, from the Tagusaris.
Excuse me, could I ask you
a few questions?
He hasn't been feeling well lately.
I'm sorry, Minoru.
-Want to call the Japan Auto Federation?
-You idiot. How can the police call JAF?
This will take some time.
Is it close by?
Right there.
But Asami Town is a big place.
We can't do much with just that photo.
I'm sure he didn't want to go home,
so he would be looking
for a place to stay nearby.
Like a park?
He won't be outside.
-He would be caught immediately.
-Oh, right.
The best place would be
somewhere he can get a meal
even if he doesn't have money.
I think I know a place like that.
CHILDREN'S CANTEEN
This is definitely the place.
Do these children look familiar to you?
How nostalgic.
Do you know them?
Yeah. All four of them
had a lot of trouble with their parents.
They moved from place to place
and came here around the same time.
Were they close?
They were always together
when they were here.
They often talked about
how they wanted to open
a shop together someday.
They wanted children like them,
who were facing various hardships,
to be able to come there.
Are you in contact with those four?
No, not now.
But Yuzuru stops by every now and then.
Is it Yuzuru Togo?
No, it's Yoshimoto. Yuzuru Yoshimoto.
Have you ever heard the name Togo?
I don't think so…
Then, do you know
where Yuzuru Yoshimoto is?
Oh, he's been visiting
his mother's nursing home.
That woman in the wheelchair
is Yuzuru Yoshimoto's mother.
I heard she was ill…
She has always had a chronic illness,
and Yuzuru has been
caring for her until now.
This nursing home looks awfully pricey.
I'm home.
A souvenir.
-Isn't it just from a convenience store?
-One in Akita!
They're all the same.
I even found the gummies you like!
How was Fumi?
Was it no good?
She hadn't been in contact with Tsuda.
I couldn't talk
to the factory manager either.
Why was Tsuda looking into that factory?
Does it have anything to do with the case?
I have no idea at all.
What about the key?
They say it's used for lockers,
desk drawers, padlocks…
All sorts of things.
It's a very common type.
At this rate, even if we had 100 years…
What about Dad's desk?
The drawer of that desk was always locked.
Then…
it might be related to the factory.
Next week, I'll be going to Hida.
It will be okay.
You don't have to worry about a thing.
How was Akita?
The last of the four is Yuzuru Yoshimoto.
It wasn't Togo.
What?
Togo is likely the mastermind.
Probably chased down the four
who ran off with the gold.
Then, isn't Yoshimoto in danger?
Yoshimoto also lives in Kanagawa,
and the police are currently
staking out his home.
They plan to wait until morning,
then take him into custody.
But…
maybe we should've left them alone.
Why?
Yoshimoto is a young caregiver,
and Yokokura's father was in debt.
They must've been desperate to survive.
Even as kids.
I suppose so.
No one came to visit Yoshimoto.
Togo isn't showing up either.
I wonder if Saki Yokokura is okay?
First Division is chasing it,
but hasn't found her yet.
The apartment's security camera?
Apparently, the whole
camera unit was taken.
The four of them
all ran to Kanagawa, only for this…
It's because they were stupid
and robbed people.
He's out.
You're Yuzuru Yoshimoto, right?
Guess I don't even need to ask.
Please come with us to the station.
I was deceived.
What do you mean by that?
Saki called me.
The four of us will steal gold.
I was invited by a man named Togo.
He's the mastermind.
He said the owner just wants to pretend
the gold was stolen, for tax purposes.
Togo said the police
wouldn't even chase us.
It's a fake robbery!
The reward was 300,000 yen per person.
What?
You would commit robbery
for such a small amount?
We didn't think we would get caught.
And for us, that was enough.
With 300,000 yen,
I could hire a caregiver for my mother.
Even if only for a short time,
I could finally be free.
In reality, you ended up being chased
by the police and Togo.
We had no choice but to run!
Hey, Kudo.
When that happens,
you turn yourself in.
Let's go.
Thank you.
After fleeing from Akita,
they turned the gold into cash.
It seems there was
an unlicensed pawnshop in Yokohama.
They each took 100 million
to pay off debts.
or put their parents in facilities.
They were finally liberated
from their parents.
And Togo deceived those four?
Can we trace Togo
through Yuzuru Yoshimoto?
No.
He says he never met him
or even contacted him.
So in the end, the only connection
is Saki Yokokura, who was kidnapped.
-Thank you!
-Thanks for the meal.
Oh, what do you want, Haruko?
A beer, please.
Sure thing.
I heard from Minoru.
He said Tsuda is dead.
He said, they didn't get
anything out of him in the end.
Yeah.
Here.
This is on the house.
Wow, how nostalgic.
Mogi's fried rice!
Do you remember it? Minoru’s birthday.
How could I forget?
I put candles in the fried rice.
How did you ever think of that?
I just wanted to do something for him.
At that time, we couldn't afford
to buy a cake.
But, he looked so incredibly happy.
Back then, they were like
ordinary kids you would see anywhere.
But I suppose I was wrong.
If I had stayed close to them
and supported them,
they might have had a different future.
By now, Minoru would have become
a forensic scientist, and Makoto…
What are you saying?
You supported them well.
I hope one day,
we can laugh like that again.
Yeah.
I knew I would find you here.
I went to the shop
to try to sell you this.
VOICES OF THE DEAD
Is this Tsuda's?
I don't need it anymore.
You mean there's another culprit
besides Tsuda?
Isn't there anything you can remember?
You're the only one who saw the culprit.
It was dark,
and they were wearing a hood and a mask.
I'm sorry.
I've asked you so many times.
So you have no clues at all.
No…
There's one thing left.
Haruko.
Introduce me to a good pawnshop.
If you're looking for a fight,
I'll fight you.
Do you know a shop
in Yokohama called Suiren-do?
That place was flagged by police,
and its owner fled back
to his country six months ago.
That's why I want to know
about shops that "cross the line."
You can't keep gold bars
with a trail on them forever.
Togo must want to cash them out.
There's no time. Hurry up.
I can't tell you anything, Makoto.
What?
Sorry, but I can't sell out my colleagues.
Look into it yourselves.
Haruko.
We have our own rules over here!
YUGO HIRANAKA MURDER CASE AUTOPSY RESULTS
Are these the forensics results
for Yugo Hiranaka?
Yes.
I read Yuzuru Yoshimoto's statement.
He says Hiranaka had no prior
connection with Togo.
If they weren't acquaintances,
the footprints
in the parking lot bother me.
Footprints?
Because it was raining, only the
footprints in the perimeter remained,
but Togo's stride is clearly shorter
than Hiranaka's.
What?
Please send Togo's security footage
for gait analysis.
But we can't identify
without a subject for comparison.
I don't mind.
I just want to know more about their gait.
On it.
KAWADA PAWNSHOP
He might have already cashed it in.
It has been three days
since Togo ran off with Hiranaka's gold.
Even if Yokokura still had her gold left,
she was kidnapped two days ago.
Hello?
That shop wasn't it, huh?
If you're messing with me, I'm hanging up.
It seems a certain pawnshop
just received some gold bars.
What?
I asked shops I know to contact me
if something comes up.
Connections are important, you know.
If you don't hurry, you won't catch them.
The shop's name is Kiho in Yokohama.
Drive!
Yes.
I wonder if Togo is still at the shop.
What's wrong?
The variance in the depths of the wounds…
-It's due to a lack of muscle strength.
-What?
After analyzing Togo's gait
on the camera footage,
there is an approximately 90% probability…
that Togo is a woman.
KIHO PAWNSHOP
Mr. Tagusari?
Yokokura.
Oh, no…
I'm busted, aren't I?
I went to the trouble
of cutting my own arm, too.
Can I have a smoke?
Since it's my last.
You're Togo, aren't you?
Togo was…
the debt collector
who used to come to our house.
Every single day…
he would bang on the door,
saying, "Pay back the money!"
That voice got stuck in my ears,
so I ended up using his name.
So from the beginning,
there never was a man named Togo.
Aiko Mizusawa realized that, didn't she?
That girl…
for someone so unfriendly,
her intuition was sharp.
Hey.
Togo…
doesn't actually exist, does he?
What?
Saki, you made him up.
I tried to make it seem
like a misunderstanding.
I told Yugo that Aiko
was planning to betray us.
You mean Aiko is trying
to turn herself in?
If we threaten her a little,
Aiko might change her mind.
We thought if we set the fire
while I was at work,
we could make Aiko believe Togo existed.
I never imagined she would be home.
The police are here.
We can't run anymore.
That was an accident. It's not your fault.
I'm going to turn myself in.
I have to tell them
I thought Aiko wasn't--
Wait a minute.
I'm going to the police
to tell them everything.
There was no turning back anymore.
I don't particularly have any regrets.
I wish I had been born
into a house like that.
The children at that canteen
all needed money.
We had to either live without dreams
or do bad stuff.
But…
if you have money, everything changes.
As long as you have money…
And how did that turn out?
Once you got the money,
did it go as you planned?
The reason I turned out like this
is all because of my parents.
It’s all your fault.
"If not for you,
I wouldn't have suffered like this."
All worthless parents
say that to their children.
But…
because those kids don't want to trouble
their parents, they can't ask for help.
Even when told,
"I wish I had never given birth to you,"
they still can't abandon their parents.
It’s pathetic, isn't it?
She confessed to the crimes.
I see.
That vehicle…
It was delivered
to Aiko Mizusawa's home today.
Mizusawa's?
According to the dealer,
she talked about how
she was going to start
a shop with her friends.
And she seemed so happy.
Mizusawa
hadn't spent a single yen of that gold.
The money you spent,
she probably intended
to earn and pay it back.
With the dream you had back then.
When we grow up,
let's run a shop together.
What kind of shop?
A place like this,
where all kinds of kids can come.
That sounds good!
It really would've been better
if Togo existed.
Let's go.
You seem curious, so I'll tell you.
When I was a child,
my father chose another woman,
and my parents divorced.
She was flashier
and more beautiful than my mother.
After that, my mother started obsessively
buying clothes and makeup,
and when the money in our house ran out…
She began to force me to shoplift.
If I had made one wrong move,
I could have been one of those four.
But…
your family environment
doesn't decide everything.
The path you walk is up to you.
Hey.
Say something.
I don't have anything to say.
I know that
you won't make a mistake again.
Hey.
What was our dad like?
Was he decent?
Dad was hungover
for most of his mornings off.
He did smell like booze.
One time, Mom even poured
hot water on him to wake him up.
Oh, yes, that happened.
You have a good memory!
I've forgotten quite a bit.
I'm forgetting more and more things.
It can't be helped.
You were only five back then.
I'm jealous of you, Makoto.
It's no use. It doesn't fit.
What’s inside?
Few dads would make their kids
something like this.
Minoru?
Makoto.
You saw it from here, right?
I don't care about that!
Let me hear your side. Hey!
-I'm busy, go home.
-No!
That guy…
I wonder what he wanted to hear from Dad?
I'll try going to Fumi's too.
I'll talk to the factory manager too.
What’s wrong?
If we investigate further,
we might find out things
we don't want to know.
Why was Dad complicit
in something like that?
I killed them.
He won't speak at all.
You have a hidden agenda, don't you?
Subtitle translation by: Nix S.