No wonder you were looking
for Hong the other day.
Everyone on the island knows about it.
But why do you think that kid
has a way to break the wish?
My friend said Hong doesn't seem
like an ordinary person.
Before this, did he say anything to you?
No.
Even if he had said something,
I wouldn't have paid much attention.
You know, in a doctor's eyes,
there are only two types of people.
One is the sick, and the other is the healthy.
So, I don't think
there's anything special about him.
I see.
But...
Mr. Hua, it's been so many years.
Have you really never thought
of going back to the main island?
Just once.
When my mentor was about to pass away,
I bought a ferry ticket
to rush back and see him.
Suddenly, a storm broke out,
causing the ferry to be canceled.
After that, whenever I bought a ticket,
something unexpected would always happen,
preventing me from returning
to the main island.
So, this must be the consequence
of your wish, Mr. Hua.
Even if you want to go back, you can't.
That's fine.
My self-exile is for atonement.
So, life shouldn't be too easy for me.
Not being able to see family and friends
is a burden I should bear.
But Mr. Hua, don't you think
the price is too high?
But to me, a wish is a choice.
Whether it's a gain or a loss
depends on how you look at it.
As for...
whether the wish can be broken,
I don't really care that much.
I accept it all.
And I'm willing to face it.
So, I'll continue to fight against the wish.
I don't want to give up on myself.
I want to get He Xiang Yong back.
This is my way of dealing with it.
Thank you, Mr. Hua.
Mr. Hua...
Although you say it so nonchalantly,
I can feel that you haven't really let it go.
Actually, there's no need to let it go.
Just reconcile with it.
Just embrace it.
Be brave and accept
the broken version of yourself.
Then, you can become a better person.
I truly hope you can go back
to the main island to save people one day.
I can save people while staying here, too.
I also hope you can save yourself, Mr. Hua.
Rescue the version of yourself
who's still stuck in that year.
Mom, I'm home!
Oh, so you still know how to come home?
I thought you'd become a main islander.
Don't be like that.
I brought a surprise for you.
I brought it back for you.
The thing you nag about every morning.
Chocola BB Plus from Japan.
Are you looking for a salary advance?
No. Don't you nag about it every morning?
Vitamin B gives you good energy.
That's rare.
You actually restocked it for me.
Of course.
After all, gifting health is trendy now. Better than flowers.
Didn't you say taking this
can supplement nutrients and keep you healthy?
It gives you a healthy glow
and keeps you beautiful forever.
You're such a sweet talker.
Did you win the receipt or the lottery?
Bingo! I won the jackpot.
I checked out a piece of land the other day.
- I think the location of that land...
- Wait, I didn't mean that lottery.
I won the lottery in love.
Can you get to the point?
Yesterday, I confessed to Hama-chan.
You like Hama-chan?
That sounds so familiar.
When did I say that?
How come I didn't know?
There's a lot you don't know.
Tell me. What else don't I know?
Nothing.
Anyway, just remember one thing.
Hama-chan was the one chasing me.
Hama-chan likes me.
That's why I confessed to him.
So, are you two planning
to have a long-distance relationship?
Let me tell you, it's a huge test.
You need to be prepared.
What long-distance?
The pier is so close to our house.
No, Zhong came for ice yesterday.
He said Hama-chan wants to see the world.
He's planning to sign with the long-haul fleet.
Oh, if he hasn't told you yet,
it means he might still be deciding.
Right? It's fine, it's fine.
It's fine.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- All right.
I have a new sailor from Japan.
You speak Japanese?
Can you go talk to him for me?
Tell him to be more of a team player.
I'll treat you to sashimi later.
Okay, great.
Is he from Japan?
Don't mess with me.
I'm sorry. Newbie.
Use this. Be careful.
Don't generalize.
Not every Japanese person likes ramen,
reading comics, and playing video games.
Generalize?
You know big words!
I have to tell my mom. Hurry up.
- Stop recording.
- Come on, say another one.
One last one.
"Pot calling the kettle black."
"You can't judge a book by its cover."
You're really good!
Li Wan Zhe. What are you doing?
Hi.
You said you had something to tell me.
So, you just wanted me to drink with you.
Cheers.
I don't want to.
Stop drinking so much.
What are you doing?
Are you crazy? Calm down.
Shut up.
Put me down.
Are you drunk?
Yes, I'm drunk.
Li Wan Zhe.
Are you serious?
I've never been more serious.
Then to you, what is love?
Love is a fleeting eternity.
Isn't being together every day
and living life happily enough?
Then what about me?
You are someone I like very, very much.
No matter where I am,
you'll always be in my heart.
If anyone tries to hit on you abroad,
you must tell them
that you already have a master.
Understand?
I want to be in love. Just like fireworks.
- Whoosh!
- Bang!
Could it be that all of this...
was granted by a wish?
I'm tired.
I can give you a massage.
It's okay.
Let's just sleep, okay?
Where am I?
Dad.
Li Wan Zhe.
He Xiang Yong.
Chen Hao Wei.
Don't waste your breath.
Hong, you finally showed up.
You can help me, right?
Why do you think I can help you?
Since you chose to abandon He Xiang Yong,
he won't be coming back.
That is something even I cannot change.
Your wish.
Your choice.
Even if you regret it now,
you have to accept it.
I won't accept it!
Then I'll just cancel the wish, okay?
I don't want to be Zhong Xiao You anymore.
Give He Xiang Yong back to me, okay?
Oh, humans.
The true value of a wish
is not in what you gain.
It's in how you face it.
- Even if the final outcome is what you call "loss."
- Dad.
Chen Hao Wei.
You still have to experience it fully.
Otherwise, what a waste it would be.
I beg you. I was wrong.
I was wrong. I'll cancel the wish, okay?
I don't want to be Zhong Xiao You anymore.
Give He Xiang Yong back to me.
Dad.
I'm He Xiang Yong.
I'm He Xiang Yong!
- Xiang Yong.
Are you kidding me?
How could I not recognize my own son?
- Xiang Yong.
- It's Xiang Yong!
Xiang Yong, how did you find time to visit?
- It's He Xiang Yong.
- He Xiang Yong.
- You don't know him either?
- No, we don't.
The one I can't let go of is He Xiang Yong.
He Xiang Yong? Who's that?
The one I've always loved
is also He Xiang Yong.
He Xiang Yong?
If he were anything like you,
I'd kick him to death.
I'm He Xiang Yong.
I'm He Xiang Yong!
Please don't go, okay?
No!
No! I'm He Xiang Yong!
I'm He Xiang Yong.
Chen Hao Wei. I'm He Xiang Yong.
Believe me. I'm He Xiang Yong.
Don't leave me, okay?
- Okay.
- I'm He Xiang Yong.
- I believe you.
- Believe me.
- Believe me. I'm really He Xiang Yong.
- I believe you.
- I do. I believe you.
- I really am.
You were having a nightmare.
I dreamt of Hong.
He wanted me to accept the cost of the wish.
To accept that He Xiang Yong no longer exists.
I don't want to. I'm He Xiang Yong.
- I'm He Xiang Yong. Believe me.
- It's okay. It's okay.
It was just a dream. It wasn't real.
No. The dream felt so real.
And things are different now.
If your dream represents
what happened in the past,
what about my dream?
It must be something
that will happen in the future.
No. I don't want He Xiang Yong to disappear.
I-If Hong won't help me, what should I do?
It's okay.
No matter what happens to you,
I'll be by your side.
Just like you said you'd catch me,
I'll catch you, too.
I don't want to disappear.
It's okay. You're safe now.
- Angela!
- Listen.
- We're here.
- When we were kids,
developing a resort on our island
was a very good choice.
And our elders have a legend.
If you throw a stone into the sea
to exchange energy with a meteor,
your wish will come true.
For a group building a resort,
this is a great selling point.
- Li Wan Zhe, come help.
- Right?
When the meteor shower arrives,
you throw the meteor fragment into the sea.
Bam!
See?
When your wish combines with that energy, it will come true!
This needs to go in the fridge quickly.
Where do you want it?
- Just take it out.
- The stone.
- Li Wan Zhe.
- Bring it here.
- Come here.
- What do you want?
Give me five minutes.
Fine.
Go ahead. Five minutes.
The cave stone.
Someone must have thrown a stone
into the sea when we were wishing.
That's the only way our wishes
could have come true.
So?
So...
So, if we go and get the stone back,
the wish might be canceled.
Are you crazy? The ocean is so vast.
How are you going to find one specific stone?
What do you mean?
Don't you want to solve this anymore?
I'm doing great right now.
I have no problems at all.
You're fine, but I'm not!
I...
Right now, no one even knows
who He Xiang Yong is anymore.
If this continues,
I might disappear from this world!
That's not my problem.
Right.
My disappearance really isn't important to you.
But what about Xiao Hai?
Things are only good with him for now.
Once your wish starts to backfire,
it'll be too late for regrets.
Are you trying to scare me?
You're scared, aren't you?
You're actually very worried, right?
Li Wan Zhe, I know you too well.
We grew up together like brothers.
You've always been a coward.
You only know how to run away.
That's why you're terrified.
You're afraid if I find that stone,
Xiao Hai won't love you anymore, right?
Anyway, I've told you about Xiao Hai.
If you keep running away,
it might end up like your wish.
Just like fireworks,
once they burn out, they're gone.
That's it.
You say I'm your brother?
Would a true friend be so selfish?
I won't let you do anything
to ruin my relationship with Xiao Hai.
You keep talking about
how you're going to disappear.
Have you ever thought maybe
you don't even deserve to exist in this world?
What did you say?
- I'm sorry.
- Screw you!
Li Wan Zhe!
Are you crazy?
What the hell do you want?
Say it!
What's your problem?
- Get up and fight!
- Stop it!
What's going on? Why are they fighting?
Stop fighting!
- Come on!
- Aren't we supposed to be moving stuff?
- Didn't you want to fight?
- Why are you fighting?
Come here!
Don't do this!
Stop it!
You guys!
That's enough!
- No fighting!
- Calm down!
Why are you fighting?
Why did you hit Wan Zhe?
Oh, for goodness' sake.
Oh dear.
It's all broken.
Are you okay?
It's a good thing Mr. He isn't here.
If he knew you got into a fight,
he'd definitely scold you.
Then let him scold me.
He might as well scold me to death.
What on earth am I doing?
Why was I so impulsive?
You were a bit too impulsive just now.
Anyway, the one who throws
the first punch is in the wrong.
That's not the point.
He's Li Wan Zhe.
We've known each other for over 20 years.
This is our first fight ever.
And I was the one who started it.
He'll never forgive me.
Actually, I don't agree with you
looking for that stone.
The sea is so vast, and the stone is so small.
How could you possibly find it?
Finding that stone is my only hope now.
I haven't even started looking yet.
Why are you shooting me down too?
No.
I just want you to be okay.
I can only be okay if I find He Xiang Yong.
Forget it.
You wouldn't understand right now.
Finding that stone is my only hope now.
I can only be okay if I find He Xiang Yong.
Just let me...
help you find He Xiang Yong.
[Epilogue]
Why point out the obvious?
Making a wish is a trial of choice.
Every choice, its beginning and its end,
has its own meaning and a reason for existing.
I don't want to just stand by and watch.
This isn't your story.
You and I are both just bystanders.
We have no right to interfere or change these choices.
You must bear the consequences of your wish,
whether they're good or bad.
When a wish comes true,
this is the path you must walk alone.
Your own subconscious
led your life to this point.
Now you're blaming it on fate?
Who was the one who started all this?
Who was the one dissatisfied with the wish,
and is now delusional enough
to want to change it?
♫  ♫
♫ ♫